mlmformula.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy

**Ugility Enterprises, Inc. and www.mlmformula.com Privacy Statement**

This document was last updated on June 13, 2008.

1\. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

Ugility Enterprises, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing www.mlmformula.com, you acknowledge and fully understand Ugility Enterprises, Inc.'s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Policy Statement.

2\. PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES

Related services and offering with links from this website, including vendor sites, affiliates, and the like have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Ugility Enterprises, Inc. services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitutde towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW E USE IT

Our company collects information in different way s from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service.

Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information may be shared with third parties, as stated herein, or in special circumstances.

In instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribe to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the purpose of offering you other products and services.

In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.

Also, with purchases, we supply our member's contact information, to our business partners, who then may contact the member by telephone after the member purchase. Sales proceeds are collected by that business partner company. We also may supply other companies with contact information, for mail offers we believe would be of interest to our members, with or without compensation from those companies. At times we may send an advertisement for a third party product, where we collect the sales proceeds, and forward the purchaser's information to that third party.

Some products and services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information.

At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and billing information (debit/credit/check).

If you are to purchase a product from our site, its partners, affiliates, or the like and choose to send the product directly to a recipient as a gift, you will be required to submit information on that person in order to fulfill the order.

PERSONAL INFORMATION USERS

www.isponsoring.com Web pages may contain tracking and electronic images that allow Ugility Enterprises, Inc. to track and count Users and Visitors to this site. And also to further market to users. Ugility Enterprises, Inc. may also include such counters and trackers in email messages in order to determine if said messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some Web Counters/Tracking devices may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These counters/trackers may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile annonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. Ugility Enterprises, Inc. prohibits trackers/counters from being used to collect or access your personal information.

5\. ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION

We sill provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant - support@mlmformula.com

6\. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

Ugility Enterprises, Inc. has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "updated" date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

7 CONTACTING US

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at:

Ugility Enterprises  
ATTN: Privact  
7645 North Union Blvd  
Suite 254  
Colorado Springs, CO 80920

Email: privacy@mlmformula.com

Telephone: 866-326-2174

8\. MISCELLANEOUS

When visitors or Members send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive.

We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. These surveys provides the opportunity to best tailor www.isponsoring.com to the needs and wants of those that visit. We make every attempt to keep collected information as protected as possible. 

UGILITY ENTERPRISES, INC. WILL NEVER SHARE SENSITIVE, PERSONAL, OR COLLECTED INFORMATION TO ANYONE NOT DEEMED APPROPRIATE BY ACTING PARTIES OF UGILITY ENTERPRISES, INC.

The term "personally identifiable information" means individually identifiable information about an individual consumer or visitor collected online by Ugility Enterprises, Inc. from an indivudual and maintained by Ugility Enterprises, Inc. in an accessible form, and may include any or all of the following:

(1) First Name  
(2) Last Name  
(3) Home or other physical or billing address, to include but not limited to street name and name of city, town, and or zip code  
(4) Contact Number   
(5) Fax Number  
(6) Any other type of information that allows the physical or online contacting of a specific individual  
(7) Any information concerning a user that the Web site or onoline service collects online, from the user, and maintains in personally identifiable form, in combination with an identifier described within this privacy polic

Services and Web sites owned or maintained by Ugility Enterprises, Inc. have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under the control of Ugility Enterprises, Inc.. While every effort is made to ensure the integrity and security of networks and systems owned or operated by Ugility Enterprises, Inc., said company cannot guarantee that implemented security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

9 POLICY FOR CHILDREN

It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen (18) years of age or older

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS ANY WEB SITE OWNED OR MAINTAINED BY UGILITY ENTERPRISES, INC.. IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS ANY MATERIAL SET FORTH BY UGILITY ENTERPRISES FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO 

Ugility Enterprises, Inc. reserves the right to alter or update this Privacy Policy without notice. It is encouraged for visitors to frequently check back to see if this document has been updated. The date of update will be clearly printed at the beginning of this document for easy reference.

© Copyright 2008 Ugility Enterprises, Inc., all rights reserved.
